http://www.spectrumplastics.com/privacy-policy

Johor, Malaysia
Mexicali (Mexico)
Johor, Malaysia
Mexicali (Mexico)
Privacy Policy
At Spectrum Plastics Group we are committed to ensuring that your personal information is protected and never misused. Protecting the confidentiality and integrity of personal data is a critical responsibility that we at Spectrum Plastics Group take seriously at all times. Spectrum Plastics Group will ensure that data is always processed in accordance with the provisions of the relevant data protection legislation, including the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
Please review the below Data Privacy Policy.
Information We Collect
Through this website, events, meetings, and phone calls, we collect. different types of information from which we can identify you. We also collect information that helps us to better understand about how you use our website, our services and what interests you. This information helps us to make our products and services more relevant to your business needs.
Information we typically collect may include:
Your title and full name
Your contact information (mailing address, telephone number(s), email address(s))
Payment and service details in regard to transactions with us
Records of meetings and interactions
Other information you share with us.
We collect this information whenever you ask us to transact with you.  For example, data collection normally takes place when you:
Request a quotation or make a purchase
Set up an account with us
Sign-up to receive automated product updates or newsletters from us
Make an enquiry at an event, such as a trade show or webinar
Agree to fill in a questionnaire about our services
Ask us a question or submit any concerns you have
Post information to our website, including opportunities to comment on, or join, discussions.
Website and Cookie Information
When you interact with our website, we automatically collect information about usage and services, such as what type of device you have and which type of internet browser or mobile device you use, whether you visited our website from another website or service and your IP address (the unique reference number that identifies your device on the internet). We use industry standard Google Analytics to give us a statistical picture of how our website is used.
Like many companies, we use “cookies” and “log files” on this website. Cookies are bits of text that are placed on your computer’s hard drive when you visit certain websites. Log files are small text files that websites automatically create when a user visits a site. We use cookies and log files to tell us, for example, whether you have visited us before or if you are a new visitor and to help us identify site features in which you may have the greatest interest. Cookies and log files may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site.
The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Remember though, without cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of all our website features.
Web Beacons
Certain pages on our site contain “web beacons” (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons allow third parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party.
Lawful Basis for Data Collection
The legal basis on which we process your personal data when you make an enquiry with us is based on our legitimate interest to understand your needs and provide you with the best products and service we can.
When you purchase products or services from us, we may collect information required to help us satisfactorily complete your transaction.  This collection process might include your: name, organization, phone number, email address, address, billing address, and VAT number (if applicable). If we process your personal data, it is because it is necessary for the performance of a contract with you, or in order to take steps at your request to enter into a contract, or to satisfy another type of transaction, such as a request for literature or product samples.
When you send us an enquiry or purchase from us, you will be given the opportunity to opt in or opt out in order to receive marketing communications in relation to our products and services by marking the relevant boxes on any appropriate forms that will be provided. We will then send you the relevant marketing communications until such time that you remove your consent. In these instances, processing is performed on the basis of your consent.
How We Use Your Information
The information we collect helps us to better understand your needs and to provide you with more timely and relevant business services. We use your information to:
Deliver the services you ask for from us
Secure and verify payments
Help us review and improve our products, services and offers
Carry out market research by email
Occasionally send promotional messages about products, services and offers
To respond to your questions or concerns
Marketing Choices
We will not sell your information to marketing companies. We do send out marketing emails from time to time, but they will only be sent to you where relevant based on our existing business relationship or where you have agreed to receive these.
We also understand that you might change your mind about receiving our occasional communications. If you do not wish us to continue to contact you in this way, you can either follow the unsubscribe instructions on any of our communications or contact us by using the contact us at marketing@spectrumplasticsgroup.com
Information We Share
We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information about our website visitors, except as described here. We may share information provided by our website visitors with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. Spectrum Plastics Group will take reasonable steps to help ensure that these service providers are obligated to safeguard your information on our organization’s behalf. In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.
We reserve the right to disclose any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use personal information you have provided through this website in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice.
Information We Transfer
We may transfer the personal information we collect on this site to other countries in which we do business, but we will do so only for the purposes described above. When we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described here, even though a given country may not have the same privacy and data protection laws as the country in which you reside.
How We Protect Personal Information
We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect the personal information you provide on this site.
Accessing your personal information
You also have the right to make a request to access personal information we hold about you and to request corrections of any errors in that data. To make an access or correction request, contact us using the contact details at the end of this policy.
Data retention
We will keep hold of your data for no longer than necessary. The length of time we retain it will depend on any legal obligations we have (such as tax recording purposes), the nature of any contracts we have in place with you, the existence of your consent or our legitimate interests as a business.
Enquiries
Unless you provide consent for future contact during your enquiry, we will keep your information for as long is required to respond and complete your enquiry, and for a further 12 months, before deleting your information.
If you no longer want us to use your personal information or to provide you with services, you can request that we erase your personal information. Please note that if you request the erasure of your personal information we will retain information from deleted accounts as necessary for our legitimate business interests, to comply with the law, prevent fraud, collect fees, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with investigations, enforce the terms of service and take other actions permitted by law. The information we retain will be handled in accordance with this policy.
Information you make public or give to others
If you make your personal information available to other people, we cannot control or accept responsibility for the way they will use or manage that data. There are many ways that you can find yourself providing information to other people, like when you post a public message on a forum thread, share information via social media, or make contact with a third-party whether via our website or directly via email.
Links to Other Sites
We may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These sites may operate independently from this website and may have their own privacy notices in place. We strongly suggest you review those privacy notices if you visit any linked websites. To the extent any linked websites you visit are unrelated to Spectrum Plastics Group / Pexco, we are not responsible for their content or any use of the sites.
How you can contact us
If you have any questions about our privacy practices or the way in which we have been managing your personal information, please contact us at marketing@spectrumplasticsgroup.com
Spectrum Plastics Group Privacy Policy, effective date May 24, 2018
